# ROCÍO VARGAS

#### Full Stack Developer + Journalist

I have been generating content about culture and shows for different digital platforms and social networks for more than ten years. I worked in teams and independently, the last years remotely. I am currently training in the Certified Tech Developer career at Digital House, Mercado Libre and Globant and I am looking for my first experience in the technology industry. I invite you to visit my LinkedIn profile where my professional history is detailed.

## CONTACT

Almagro, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Mail: vargasroc@gmail.com Celular: +541554891669 Linkedin: <u>/rociovargas</u>

## EDUCATION

#### **Digital House**

Certified Tech Developer - In the second year - Back end specialization.

#### Universidad Nacional de las Artes

Bachelor of Arts Criticism - Completed first year.

## Instituto Superior de Letras Eduardo Mallea

Higher Technician in Text Correction - Completed up to the second year.

#### Instituto Superior Grafótecnico

Journalist, 2005 - 2008

## SKILLS

Java - Spring Boot - Maven - ORM Hibernate - Spring MVC, Spring Data, Spring Security - REST APIs - JWT - Swagger - MySQL - MongoDB - etwork Operating Systems (Windows, Linux) - AWS - Virtual Box - Vagrant - Docker - Scripting (Bash, PowerShell) - Terraform - Ansible - Cloud Formation - CI / CD - Monitoring - Webs - Scrum - Kanban - GIT, GITHub, GITLab.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Team Leader - Infrastructure Analyst**

Glamp House | August 2022 - September 2022

Leadership and organization of tasks.

Creation and maintenance of the Glamp House web application infrastructure, using different AWS services. Carried out within the framework of the Integrating Project of the first track of the Certified Developer Career

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Content Specialist**

El patio orgánico | 2021

#### **Argentine Community Coordinator**

BabyCenter en Español | 2016 - 2020

#### Producer Sr.

América Móvil Contenidos | 2012 - 2018

## COURSES

- AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials AWS training and certification
- Google Project Management Coursera

## LANGUAGES

English	Iltalian
Intermediate Oral Level.	Basic Oral Level.
Intermediate Written Level.	Basic Written Level.